taltopia.com 2011-08-27

# Privacy Policy

|  | 

_Last modified January 14, 2011._

Privacy Policy subject to change at discretion of Taltopia.com. At Taltopia.com we observe the following in respect to your privacy:

###  Cookies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site, and to monitor aggregate usage by users and web traffic routing on the Site. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

###  Registration Data

To enable site features, we may ask you to register. Taltopia may share this information with our web advertising partners. Taltopia is not responsible for their privacy policies and/or practices. 

###  Log Information

When you use Taltopia, our servers automatically record information that your browser normally sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include data such as your web request, IP address, and browser type. We may examine site usage patterns in aggregate to determine how we can make the site easier to use.

###  Security

Taltopia uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Taltopia and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Taltopia makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

###  User Submitted Content & User Communications

Any content you submit to the site (videos, voting, comments, etc.) will be publicly available. From time to time employees may examine this content or other user behavior to confirm that the terms of service are not being breached. When you send email or other communication to Taltopia, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We will not send you marketing emails directly from Taltopia if you use the unsubscribe link in a previous email. However Taltopia may share your information with our web advertising partners. Taltopia is not responsible for their privacy policies and/or practices.

###  Childrens' Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Taltopia does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Taltopia Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Taltopia Sites at any time or in any manner. If Taltopia learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Taltopia Sites without verified parental consent, then Taltopia will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

###  Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by Taltopia.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Taltopia.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###  Links

Taltopia.com contains links to sites. Taltopia is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Taltopia.

###  Change of Control

In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy In the event that Taltopia is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.  
  
---|---|---
